commerceguys.com 2017-02-14

# Privacy Policy | Commerce Guys

Commerce Guys operates various websites and offers many different services and products.  Through these sites, products, services and software, including software available for download from these sites, we obtain certain information from and about you.

We value your privacy and we are committed to safeguarding and preserving the privacy of our visitors. This Privacy Policy explains what information we collect, how we use that information, and other policies regarding your information and privacy. We have tried to make it as simple as possible, but if you do not understand something, please [contact us](http://commerceguys.com/inquiry).

“Commerce Guys” means Commerce Guys SAS, a French company located at 38, rue du Sentier , Paris, 75002 France, and Commerce Guys, LLC, a Michigan limited liability company located at 900 Victors Way, Suite 328, Ann Arbor, Michigan 48108, and, and may include its affiliates, subsidiaries, directors, officers, employees, agents, partners, contractors, and/or licensors (together, referred to throughout this Privacy Policy as “Commerce Guys” or “us” or “we”).

Our Privacy Policy applies to all of the services offered by Commerce Guys, including services offered on any of our websites (CommerceGuys.com, DrupalCommerce.org, Marketplace.CommerceGuys.com), but excludes services that have separate privacy policies that do not incorporate this Privacy Policy.

We update this Privacy Policy from time to time, so please review it regularly. Your continued use of our sites and services will be subject to the terms of the then-current Privacy Policy.

##  Information We Collect

We collect information that you give us or that we get from your use of our sites and services, including without limitation, the following:

Information about your use of our sites and services, including details of your visits to our sites, pages viewed and the resources that you accessed. Examples of information include device, location and traffic data.

Information specifically provided by you, including your name, telephone number, email address, physical address, login username, password, or other information that you voluntarily share with us.

##  Use of Cookies

We may use cookies to gather information about your general internet use. When used, cookies are downloaded and stored on your device. Such information, on its own, will not identify you personally. It is statistical data. Generally you can turn off the cookie function on your device, but that may prevent you from using our sites and services. Some third party services that we use, such as Google Analytics, may also place cookies on your device. This Privacy Policy does not cover the use of cookies by third parties.

##  Using Your Information

We use the information we collect from you to provide, maintain, protect and improve our sites and services, and to develop new ones. 

In addition, we may use the information for one or more of the following purposes:

  * To provide information to you that you request from us relating to our products or services.
  * To provide information to you related to products or services provided by us.
  * To inform you of any changes, offers, updates or other announcements about our sites, services or products.

Finally, if you install and use any of our products or services, such as a module or any other software, these products will report information to us, and we will collect this information.  This information may be linked to you and we may use this information to better provide technical support to you and our other customers, and to improve our sites, services and products.

##  Storing and Securing your Personal Data and Information

Our computer systems are currently based in the United States (“U.S.”), so your personal data will be processed by us in the U.S. where data protection and privacy regulations may not offer the same level of protection as in other parts of the world, such as the European Union (“EU”). If you visit and use our sites from outside the U.S., you agree to this Privacy Policy and you consent to the transfer of all such information to the U.S., which may not offer an equivalent level of protection of that required in the EU or certain other countries, and to the processing of that information as described in this Privacy Policy.

We take all reasonable measures to protect your personal data and information, and to protect our sites from unauthorized access to or unauthorized alteration, disclosure or destruction of information we maintain. 

##  Disclosing Your Information

We will not disclose your personal information to any other party other than in accordance with this Privacy Policy and in the circumstances detailed below:

  * Consent: 
    * We may disclose personal information if we have your specific consent to do so.
  * Co-sponsored activities: 
    * When you sign up for a webinar or other activity that is co-sponsored by another company, we may share your registration information with that company.
  * Third Party Services: 
    * We use trusted third party service providers, consultants and other agents to help us provide, maintain, protect and improve our sites, services and products.  We provide personal information to these parties to perform certain tasks based on our instructions and in compliance with our Privacy Policy or an equivalent level of privacy protection.
    * Examples of third party services include data storage, maintenance services, database management, web analytics, payment processing.
  * Legal: 
    * We will share personal information if we have a good-faith belief that access, use, preservation or disclosure of the information is reasonably necessary to: 
      * meet any applicable law, regulation, legal process or enforceable governmental request;
      * enforce applicable Terms of Service or any of our other agreements with you, including investigation of potential breaches;
      * detect, prevent or otherwise address fraud, security or technical issues; or
      * protect against harm to the rights, property or safety of Commerce Guys, our users and customers, or the general public, as required or permitted by law.
  * Succession: 
    * If we are involved in a merger, acquisition or asset sale, you agree that your personal information may be transferred to a third party.

If you wish to “opt-out” of having your personal information used for certain purposes, please [contact us](http://commerceguys.com/inquiry).

All information you disclose in your public profile, in forum posts, blogs, comments, issue queues, or other public portions of our sites becomes public information.  You should be careful in what you choose to disclose publicly.

##  Accessing and Updating Your Personal Information

You may have access to your personal information that we hold, and correct, amend, or delete that information where it is inaccurate, except where the burden or expense of providing access would be disproportionate to the risks to your privacy, or where the rights of persons other than you would be violated.

##  Third Party Links

We may include links to other websites which we do not control. We do not endorse these sites, nor are we responsible for the content or accuracy of any information contained on them. By clicking on a link, you are subject to their privacy policies and terms of use, and assume all risks.

##  Contacting Us

If you have any questions or concerns regarding this Privacy Policy, please [contact us](http://commerceguys.com/inquiry).

Visitors have the following options for correcting personal information or removing their information from our database in order to discontinue future communications from Commerce Guys.

  1. Click on the "Unsubscribe" link on any Commerce Guys email
  2. Send a request to [webmaster@commerceguys.com](mailto:webmaster@commerceguys.com)
  3. Send a request by mail to the following postal address: PO Box 536 , Brooklyn, MI 49230
  4. Call the following telephone number: 1-888-827-7142 to make such a request
